It must have been a dream
I couldn't tell what time it was
Couldn't seem to breathe
But it still felt like me
At least it looked like you
Remember all the things we used to do
Once again, they're coming true
Mr. Know-It-All, why'd you let it fall?
It's a bad idea to just disappear
Running towards your voice
As if I even had a choice
I had to see your smile
Ran for what seemed like miles
Walked for what seemed like days
Just getting further and
Further and further and further away, oh
It's time to let it go
Just let it be a ghost
Haunting me in my sleep
But first I need to know
Tell me all your plans
Anything that you can
To keep me in, so far from you
So tell me what you meant
Mr. Know-It-All, why'd you let it fall?
It's a bad idea to just disappear